{
	"male": {
		"hair": [
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm1","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm1","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm10","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm10","hair_front":"hair_front_bm10","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm10"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm11","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm11","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm12","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm12","hair_front":"hair_front_bm12","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm12"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm13","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm13","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm14","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm14","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm14"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm15","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm15","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm16","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm16","hair_front":"hair_front_bm16","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm16"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm17","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm17","hair_front":"hair_front_bm17","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm18","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm18","hair_front":"hair_front_bm18","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm18"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm19","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm19","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm2","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm2","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm2"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm20","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm20","hair_front":"hair_front_bm20","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm20"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm21","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm21","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm22","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm22","hair_front":"hair_front_bm22","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm22"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm23","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm23","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm24","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm24","hair_front":"hair_front_bm24","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm24"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm25","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm25","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm26","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm26","hair_front":"hair_front_bm26","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm26"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm27","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm27","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm28","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm28","hair_front":"hair_front_bm28","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm28"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm29","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm29","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm3","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm3","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm30","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm30","hair_front":"hair_front_bm30","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm30"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm31","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm31","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm32","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm32","hair_front":"hair_front_bm32","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm32"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm33","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_blank","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm34","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm34","hair_front":"hair_front_bm34","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm35","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm35","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm36","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm36","hair_front":"hair_front_bm36","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm36"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm37","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm37","hair_front":"hair_front_bm37","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm37"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm38","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm38","hair_front":"hair_front_bm38","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm38"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm39","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm39","hair_front":"hair_front_bm39","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm39"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm4","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm4","hair_front":"hair_front_bm4","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm4"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm40","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm40","hair_front":"hair_front_bm40","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm40"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm41","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm41","hair_front":"hair_front_bm41","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm41"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm42","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm42","hair_front":"hair_front_bm42","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm42"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm43","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm43","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm44","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm44","hair_front":"hair_front_bm44","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm44"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm45","forehead":"forehead_bm3","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm45","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm46","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm46","hair_front":"hair_front_bm46","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm46"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm47","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm47","hair_front":"hair_front_bm47","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm47"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm48","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm48","hair_front":"hair_front_bm48","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm48"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm5","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm5","hair_front":"hair_front_bm5","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm5"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm6","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm6","hair_front":"hair_front_bm6","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm6"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm7","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm7","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm8","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm8","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm8"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm9","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm9","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"}
		],
		"facialHair": [
			{"beard":"beard_bm4_1","stachin":"_blank","stachout":"stachout_bm4_1"},
			{"beard":"beard_bm1_1","stachin":"stachin_bm1_1","stachout":"stachout_bm1_1"},
			{"beard":"beard_bm3_1","stachin":"_blank","stachout":"stachout_bm5_1"},
			{"beard":"beard_bm3_1","stachin":"stachin_bm1_1","stachout":"stachout_bm1_1"},
			{"beard":"beard_bm2_1","stachin":"stachin_bm1_1","stachout":"stachout_bm1_1"},
			{"beard":"beard_bm3_1","stachin":"_blank","stachout":"stachout_bm6_1"},
			{"beard":"beard_bm3_1","stachin":"_blank","stachout":"stachout_bm7_1"},
			{"beard":"beard_bm4_1","stachin":"stachin_bm1_1","stachout":"stachout_bm1_1"},
			{"beard":"beard_bm4_1","stachin":"_blank","stachout":"stachout_bm5b_1"},
			{"beard":"beard_bm4_1","stachin":"_blank","stachout":"stachout_bm6b_1"},
			{"beard":"beard_bm4_1","stachin":"_blank","stachout":"stachout_bm7b_1"},
			{"beard":"_blank","stachin":"_blank","stachout":"_blank"}
		],
		"mouth": [
			{"mouth":"mouth_bm1","tongue":"tongue_bm1_1"},
			{"mouth":"mouth_bm3","tongue":"tongue_bm1_1"},
			{"mouth":"mouth_bm5","tongue":"tongue_bm1_1"}
		],
		"brow": [
			{"brow_L":"brow_bm1","brow_R":"brow_bm1"},
			{"brow_L":"brow_bm3","brow_R":"brow_bm3"},
			{"brow_L":"brow_bm5","brow_R":"brow_bm5"},
			{"brow_L":"brow_bm7","brow_R":"brow_bm7"}
		],
		"faceLines": [
			{"detail_T":"_blank"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm1"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm2"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm3"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm4"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm5"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm6"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm7"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm8"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm9"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm10"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm11"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm12"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm13"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm14"}
		],
		"cheekDetails": [
			{"detail_L":"_blank","detail_R":"_blank"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm1","detail_R":"detail_L_bm1"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm7","detail_R":"detail_L_bm7"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm8","detail_R":"detail_L_bm8"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm9","detail_R":"detail_L_bm9"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm10","detail_R":"detail_L_bm10"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm11","detail_R":"detail_L_bm11"}
		],
		"eyeDetails": [
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm1","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm1"},
			{"detail_E_L":"_blank","detail_E_R":"_blank"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm2","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm2"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm3","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm3"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm4","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm4"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm5","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm5"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm6","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm6"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm7","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm7"}
		],
		"nose": [
			{"nose":"nose_bm1"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm3"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm5"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm7"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm9"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm11"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm13"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm15"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm17"}
		],
		"headwear": [
			{"hat":"_blank"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmkufi"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmturban"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmyamulke"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmpatka"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmart1"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmbackwards"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmarmy"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmart4"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmart6"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmart7"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmart9"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmartsylvain"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmbiker"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmtoque"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmpoorboy"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmgolfback"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmfargo"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmknit"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmcap"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmrasta"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmheadphones"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmstring"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmsweatband"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmvisor"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmsanta"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmdevil"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmfootball"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmsun"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmfloppy"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmhairwrap"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmclochet"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmheadband"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmearmuff"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmflower"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmbow"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmhairclip"}
		],
		"glasses": [
			{"glasses":"_blank"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm1"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm1d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm2"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm2d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm3"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm3d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm4"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm4d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm5"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm5d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm6"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm6d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm7"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm7d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm8"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm8d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm9"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm9d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm10"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm10d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm11"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm12"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm13"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm13d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm14"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm15"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm15d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm16"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm16d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm17"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm17d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm18"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm19"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm19d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm20"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm21"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm22"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm23"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm24"}
		],
		"build": [
			{"body_type":0},
			{"body_type":1},
			{"body_type":2},
			{"body_type":3},
			{"body_type":5}
		],
		"colors": [
			{"lips":"ff9866"},
			{"skin":"ffcc99"},
			{"brow":"4f453e"},
			{"hair":"926715"},
			{"eyes":"36a7e9"},
			{"facialHair":"6f4b4b"}
		],
		"proportion": [0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8],
		"outfit": [
			889161,889163,889164,889165,889166,889167,889175,889176,889177,889178,889179,889180,889196,889197,889198,889199,
			889200,889201,889506,889507,889508,889509,889510,889511,889232,889233,889235,889236,889237,889238,889219,889220,
			889221,889222,889223,889224
		],
		"sex":1
	},
	"female": {
		"hair": [
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm1","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm1","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm10","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm10","hair_front":"hair_front_bm10","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm10"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm11","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm11","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm12","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm12","hair_front":"hair_front_bm12","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm12"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm13","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm13","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm14","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm14","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm14"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm15","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm15","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm16","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm16","hair_front":"hair_front_bm16","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm16"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm17","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm17","hair_front":"hair_front_bm17","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm18","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm18","hair_front":"hair_front_bm18","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm18"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm19","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm19","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm2","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm2","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm2"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm20","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm20","hair_front":"hair_front_bm20","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm20"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm21","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm21","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm22","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm22","hair_front":"hair_front_bm22","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm22"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm23","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm23","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm24","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm24","hair_front":"hair_front_bm24","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm24"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm25","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm25","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm26","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm26","hair_front":"hair_front_bm26","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm26"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm27","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm27","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm28","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm28","hair_front":"hair_front_bm28","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm28"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm29","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm29","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm3","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm3","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm30","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm30","hair_front":"hair_front_bm30","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm30"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm31","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm31","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm32","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm32","hair_front":"hair_front_bm32","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm32"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm33","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_blank","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm34","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm34","hair_front":"hair_front_bm34","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm35","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm35","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm36","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm36","hair_front":"hair_front_bm36","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm36"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm37","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm37","hair_front":"hair_front_bm37","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm37"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm38","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm38","hair_front":"hair_front_bm38","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm38"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm39","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm39","hair_front":"hair_front_bm39","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm39"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm4","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm4","hair_front":"hair_front_bm4","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm4"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm40","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm40","hair_front":"hair_front_bm40","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm40"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm41","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm41","hair_front":"hair_front_bm41","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm41"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm42","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm42","hair_front":"hair_front_bm42","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm42"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm43","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm43","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm44","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm44","hair_front":"hair_front_bm44","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm44"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm45","forehead":"forehead_bm3","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm45","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm46","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm46","hair_front":"hair_front_bm46","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm46"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm47","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm47","hair_front":"hair_front_bm47","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm47"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm48","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm48","hair_front":"hair_front_bm48","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm48"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm5","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_bm5","hair_front":"hair_front_bm5","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm5"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm6","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_bm6","hair_front":"hair_front_bm6","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm6"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm7","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm7","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm8","forehead":"forehead_bm2","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm8","hairbottom":"hairbottom_bm8"},
			{"cranium":"cranium_bm9","forehead":"forehead_bm1","hair_back":"hair_back_blank","hair_front":"hair_front_bm9","hairbottom":"hairbottom_blank"}
		],
		"blush": [
			{"detail_L2_L":"_blank","detail_L2_R":"_blank"},
			{"detail_L2_L":"detail_L2_bm1","detail_L2_R":"detail_L2_bm1"}
		],
		"mouth": [
			{"mouth":"mouth_bm2","tongue":"tongue_bm1_2"},
			{"mouth":"mouth_bm4","tongue":"tongue_bm1_2"},
			{"mouth":"mouth_bm6","tongue":"tongue_bm1_2"}
		],
		"brow": [
			{"brow_L":"brow_bm2","brow_R":"brow_bm2"},
			{"brow_L":"brow_bm4","brow_R":"brow_bm4"},
			{"brow_L":"brow_bm6","brow_R":"brow_bm6"},
			{"brow_L":"brow_bm12","brow_R":"brow_bm12"},
			{"brow_L":"brow_bm14","brow_R":"brow_bm14"}
		],
		"faceLines": [
			{"detail_T":"_blank"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm1"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm2"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm3"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm4"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm5"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm6"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm7"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm8"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm9"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm10"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm11"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm12"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm13"},
			{"detail_T":"detail_T_bm14"}
		],
		"cheekDetails": [
			{"detail_L":"_blank","detail_R":"_blank"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm1","detail_R":"detail_L_bm1"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm7","detail_R":"detail_L_bm7"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm8","detail_R":"detail_L_bm8"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm9","detail_R":"detail_L_bm9"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm10","detail_R":"detail_L_bm10"},
			{"detail_L":"detail_L_bm11","detail_R":"detail_L_bm11"}
		],
		"eyeDetails": [
			{"detail_E_L":"_blank","detail_E_R":"_blank"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm1","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm1"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm2","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm2"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm3","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm3"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm4","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm4"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm5","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm5"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm6","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm6"},
			{"detail_E_L":"detail_E_bm7","detail_E_R":"detail_E_bm7"}
		],
		"nose": [
			{"nose":"nose_bm2"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm4"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm6"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm8"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm10"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm12"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm14"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm18"},
			{"nose":"nose_bm20"}
		],
		"eyeshadow": [
			{"detail_E2_L":"_blank","detail_E2_R":"_blank"},
			{"detail_E2_L":"detail_E2_bm1","detail_E2_R":"detail_E2_bm1","eyelid_L":"eyelid_bm2_2","eyelid_R":"eyelid_bm2_2"}
		],
		"headwear": [
			{"hat":"_blank"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmhijab"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmyamulke"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmknit"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmhairwrap"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmcap"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmclochet"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmsun"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmart9"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmtoque"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmart1"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmbackwards"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmartsylvain"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmheadphones"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmearmuff"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmheadband"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmbow"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmflower"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmhairclip"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmstring"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmsweatband"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmfloppy"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmdevil"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmfargo"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmrasta"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmvisor"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmfootball"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmsanta"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmbiker"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmarmy"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmart4"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmart6"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmart7"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmgolfback"},
			{"hat":"hat_bmpoorboy"}
		],
		"glasses": [
			{"glasses":"_blank"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm1"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm1d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm2"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm2d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm3"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm3d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm4"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm4d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm5"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm5d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm6"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm6d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm7"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm7d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm8"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm8d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm9"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm9d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm10"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm10d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm11"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm12"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm13"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm13d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm14"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm15"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm15d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm16"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm16d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm17"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm17d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm18"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm19"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm19d"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm20"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm21"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm22"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm23"},
			{"glasses":"glasses_bm24"}
		],
		"build": [
			{"body_type":0},
			{"body_type":1},
			{"body_type":2},
			{"body_type":3},
			{"body_type":5}
		],
		"chestSize": [
			{"breast_type":0},
			{"breast_type":1},
			{"breast_type":3}
		],
		"colors": [
			{"blush":"ff9999"},
			{"lips":"ff9866"},
			{"skin":"ffcc99"},
			{"brow":"4f453e"},
			{"hair":"926715"},
			{"eyes":"36a7e9"},
			{"eyeshadow":"b88eb6"}
		],
		"proportion": [0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8],
		"outfit": [
			889168,889169,889170,889171,889173,889174,889499,889501,889502,889503,889504,889505,889202,889203,889204,889205,
			889206,889207,889208,889209,889210,889211,889213,889214,889225,889227,889228,889229,889230,889231,889513,889514,
			889515,889516,889517,889518
		],
		"sex":2
	}
}
